Thorton Hall 912, 1600 Holloway Ave, San Francisco, CA 94132 1 (415) 767-8984

m.cadier.kim@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I do research in combinatorial optimization and machine learning. My mathematical work deals with a class of polytopes related to classical root systems and submodular set functions. More broadly I am interested in algebraic combinatorics and discrete geometry. I also build machine learning algorithms for medical applications. Currently I am interested applications of convolutional neural networks to eye diseases.

WORK HISTORY

Researcher in Machine Vision

UCSF Proctor Foundation May, 2015 - present

San Francisco, CA May, 2015 - present We recieved a grant to investigate machine learning algorithms to classify images of eyelids. I worked under the lead biostatistician to develop a grading algorithm according to WHO guidlines for identifying trachoma infection.

Lecturer in Mathematics

San Francisco State University

San Francisco, CA

September, 2014 - December, 2015

I have been the principal instructor for several sections of college algebra and precalculus. I helped develop and administer a large online calculus coursef for 200+ students each semester.

Data Science Associate

Argyle Data

San Mateo, CA

June, 2014 - February, 2015

I worked alongside the senior software engineer to research, prototype, and develop

machine learning and statistical algorithms for fraud detection.

Papers

A Characterization of Generalized Permutohedra for the Classical Reflection

Groups, 2015, (thesis)

 $Transfer\ learning\ from\ Convolutional\ Neural\ Networks\ for\ features\ to\ classify\ Trachoma\ infection,\ with\ Dr.\ Travis\ Porco\ and\ Dr.\ Kazunori\ Okada,\ 2015,\ (in$

progress)

EDUCATION

SFSU: MA, Mathematics, 2015

SFSU: BA, Philosophy, Mathematics, 2012

University of Paris 1: Visiting Student, Philosophy, Logic, Mathematics, 2009-

2011

Programming Languages English French (Fluent) Java Python Matlab Julia